Information Systems Engineer / Analist

Carmela Roitzaid | Karmiel | 1991 | Carmela1991.r@gmail.com | 050-308-6660 | https://carmelaroit.github.io/

Summary

Information Systems Engineer.

Experience in writing requirements documents and characterizing the system (including description of the organization and data structure, editing Mockups Design, UML).

Experience in training and development of content and training materials.

Experience in developing software in **C programming** in a **Linux environment**.

Using development tools: **Bootstrap, Visual Studio, VNC, MobaXterm, Matlab, MySQL, SQLite, PyCharm, Git, Arena, Visual Paradigm**

Work Experience

2021-2018:

<u>Magshimim program (cyber education)</u> - instruction in programming languages (C language) and computer structure.

2017 -2018:

<u>Psagot Education Association</u> - volunteer work, guidance of school children in various subjects. 2017-2016:

<u>Davidson Institute</u> - volunteer work, guidance at the Museum of Science for Children.

Education

2021-2016:

B.Sc in Information Systems Engineering / Braude College-

<u>Major:</u> Software Development in Information Systems Engineering.

<u>Final project:</u> Research and development of a technology system based on facial recognition using deep metric learning methods.

<u>Extensive experience:</u> in writing requirements documents and characterizing software systems. 2012-2010:

Practical Electronics and Computers / Braude College-

<u>Final Project:</u> Develops a technological product "Baby Control System", the system allows to check the baby's condition at night with the help of sensors and signal processing circuits, 89C5131 processor, RF transmission system and reception, LCD matrix.

2010-2007:

Theoretical matriculation / Aloni Yitzhak.

Military Experience

2014-2012:

<u>Commander and instructor /Air Force</u> - management and leadership of teams, responsibility for content development and training in the field of electronic systems.

Languages

Hebrew: Native | English: Advanced | Russian: Intermediate

Courses and Training

2021:

<u>SQL - MySQL for Data Analytics and Business Intelligence /Udemy - SQL for Business Analysis, Marketing, and Data Management.</u>

<u>Digital simulation /Braude Collage</u> - planning, analyzing and modeling various systems and organizations with an emphasis on streamlining and improving the proper management of resources. Modeling using Arena software.

2020:

<u>Advanced WEB technologies /Braude Collage</u> - client application development, jQuery, Javascript, CSS, HTML ANGULAR, ASP.NET server application development.

<u>Database systems / Braude Collage</u> - ERD model design, knowledge and use of the SQL language, query optimization, normalization methodology and parallelism control.

<u>User interfaces /Braude Collage</u> - building a prototype, designing screens and forms (GUI), working with tools such as, scene builder javaFX.

web developer / Udemy - web development - HTML, CSS, JS, Node.